Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Medical Related Topical Files
    - Ophthalmology
      - Little Girl at Park, 1993 (Box 23)
      - Microarray Labs, 4 MDs, Lasix Surgery Room, Lab Construction (Box 23)
      - Mother and Son: Home, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Occupational Health Nursing Eye Care Seminar, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Outside Trailers, 2001 (Box 23)
      - Patient at Home, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Stillman [Skillman] Clinic
        - 1993 (Box 23)
        - (Waiting Area), 1993 (Box 23)
      - Testimonials
        - Mother and Daughter, 2000 (Box 23)
        - Monroe Family, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Ypsilanti-Kellogg Eye Center, 1999 (Box 23)
    - Ophthalmology/Optometry/Opticianry, 1990; undated (Box 23)
    - Oral Surgery, 1999 (Box 23)
    - Organogensis, 1996
      - Symposium
        - 1996 (Box 23)
        - Reception, 1996 (Box 23)
    - Orthopedic Surgery, 1999; undated; negatives and prints (Box 23)
    - Orthopedics
      - Instruments
        - 1993 (Box 23)
        - 1992 (Box 23)
      - Pelvis, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Model on Operation Table, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Research Lab, 2000 (Box 23)
    - Orthotics, 1998 (Box 23)
    - OSMA, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Otolaryngology, 1996; 1999; 2000
      - Charles and Barbara Krause Lectureship, 1996 (Box 23)
      - Group, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Kemink Lecture, 2001 (Box 23)
      - Speakers in memory of ..., 1999 (Box 23)
    - Pathology
      - Brochure, 1998(?) (Box 23)
      - Pathology (prints), undated (Box 23)
    - Patients from Contagious Hospital (mostly children) prints, undated (Box 23)
    - Pediatric Cardiology
      - Cardiovascular Research Unit, 1998 (Box 23)
      - Grand Rounds, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Heart to Heart, 1998 (Box 23)
      - Niland Lecture
        - 1997 (Box 23)
        - 2000 (Box 23)
      - Young ICD Conference, 2001 (Box 23)
    - Pediatric Pulmonology (Box 24)
      - Catheters, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Dr. and Patient, 1995 (Box 24)
    - Pediatric Surgery, 1999 (Box 24)
    - Pediatrics
      - 2 people with certificate, 1992 (Box 24)
      - 2 women [Fredal?], undated; negatives (Box 24)
      - 5th Annual Pediatrics Residence Symposium, 1994 (Box 24)
      - 12th Annual Pediatrics Research Symposium, 1991 (Box 24)
      - 75th Anniversary Department of Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1997 (Box 24)
      - Amnon Rosenthal Professorship Dinner, 1993 (Box 24)
      - Awards Dinner at Travis Pointe (Box 24)
      - Beyer Group, 1998 (Box 24)
      - Bone Marrow Transplant, 1991; negatives (Box 24)
      - Brochure
        - [c1970 ?] (includes miscellaneous hospital scenes) (Box 24)
        - 1989 (Box 24)
        - 1991 (Box 24)
      - Burn Technique, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Cancer Center Trick or Treat, 1998 (Box 24)
      - Cervical Positioning, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Chamber Pot Award, undated (Box 24)
      - Doctors in Lab, 1994 (Box 24)
      - Dr. Dick/A. Rosenthal Prof, 1994 (Box 24)
      - Dr. Glover in Lab, 1993 (Box 24)
      - Dr. McCormick, Marcey, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Dr. Munser with Patient, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Dr. Rosen ept, 1991; negatives (Box 24)
      - Dr. Sullivan's Retirement Party, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Graduation
        - Fellowship Graduation
          - 1992, 1993 (Box 24)
          - 1993 (Box 24)
        - House Officer Graduation Group, 1996 (Box 24)
        - Pediatrics Graduate Dinner, 1994 (Box 24)
        - Pediatrics Intern Graduation, 1995 (Box 24)
      - Group of Visiting Physicians Cardiology, 1994 (Box 24)
      - House Officers Dinner, 1997 (Box 24)
      - Jeffrey Innis lecturing and patient care (prints), 1999 (Box 24)
      - Kelch Professor Reception, 1994 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Union Ballroom Pediatrics Administration, 2000 (Box 24)
      - Mother and Child, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Patient with Ivac machine (Box 24)
      - Pediatric Research, Dr. Marcey McCormick, 1991; negatives (Box 24)
      - Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases Annual Report, 2001 (Box 24)
      - Pediatrics Group at Towsley, 1989; negatives (Box 24)
      - Pediatrics Surgery 20th Anniversary (print), 1995 (Box 24)
      - Physicians Portraits, 1998 (Box 24)
      - Promoted House Officers Group, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Quads in Evenflow Car Seat, 1998 (Box 24)
      - Research Symposium, annual, 1990; negatives (Box 24)
      - Research Symposium, second annual, 1991; negatives (Box 24)
      - Sickle Cell Anemia Project, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Unidentified, 1991; negatives (Box 24)
      - Visiting Clinician Day, 1991; negatives (Box 24)
      - Visiting Clinicians Group, 1993 (Box 24)
      - Visiting Group, 1993 (Box 24)
      - Visiting Physicians Seminar, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Welcome New Faculty, 1997 (Box 24)
    - Pediatrics/Obstetrics, undated (Box 24)
    - Pharmacology
      - ISOM Lab and Osawa Lab, 1995 (Box 24)
      - Martin Luther King Day Speaker, 1993 (Box 24)
      - Panel Discussion with Mark Nickerson, undated (Box 24)
      - Pharmacology, 1989 (Box 24)
      - Radio Pharmacology Symposium, 1995 (Box 24)
      - Research Lecture, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation
      - Boots, 1999 (Box 24)
      - Group, 2001 (Box 24)
      - Island Park Picnic, 1990 (Box 24)
      - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1989 (Box 24)
      - Physical Therapy, 1999 (Box 24)
      - Polio Handicap Insert, 1989 (Box 24)
      - Rehabilitation and Prosthetics, undated (Box 24)
      - Steps of Mott, 2000 (Box 24)
      - Visiting Music Therapist, 1990 (Box 24)
    - Physical Therapy, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Physiology
      - Annual Report and Lab Shots, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Faculty Lab Shots, 2000; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Fred Karsch and Students, 2000 (Box 24)
      - Graduate Student Brochure, 1993 (Box 24)
    - Planning and Marketing
      - Audrey Lucas Retirement Party, 1999 (Box 24)
      - Brochure, Offsite Facility, 1989 (Box 24)
      - Canton Center Groundbreaking, 1999 (Box 24)
      - Dr. Ommen -- Fitness Test, 2000 (Box 24)
      - Drs. Collins and Ianuzzi in Lab, 1990 (Box 24)
      - Family Forum, 1997 (Box 24)
      - Group Shot
        - 1997 (Box 24)
        - 1998, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Heart Newsletter, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Mott Video Conference, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Primary Care, 1997 (Box 24)
      - Quality Month
        - Admitting and Business Services Team, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Agreement Signing, 1993 (Box 24)
        - Breast Care Cancer Team, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Briarwood Family Practice, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Brighton Health Center, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Cash Register Team, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Chelsea Internal Medicine Specialist, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Clinical Business Operations Team (CBOT), 1999 (Box 24)
        - Contract Signing, 1994 (Box 24)
        - Derm. Performance Team (Box 24)
        - Dr. Simon in Lab, 1993 (Box 24)
        - Faculty and Staff Resources, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Food and Nutrition Services Department Orientation, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Food and Nutrition, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Hard Hat Parade Celebration, 1993 (Box 24)
        - Howell Pediatrics, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Livonia Spec Center [Livonia Center for Special Care], 1999 (Box 24)
        - Medical Information Team, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Michigan Quality Council/Planning and Marketing Quality Leadership Award, 1994 (Box 24)
        - Mott New 6th Floor Grant Opening, 1993 (Box 24)
        - Novi Health Center, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Obstetrics and Gynecological Health Education Resources, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Pediatric New Diabetic Patient Management Team, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Promo[tional] Items, 1992 (Box 24)
        - Protective Intervention/Restraint Policy and Intervention Team, 1999 (Box 24)
        - Quality Month, 1998 (Box 24)
        - Sedation Analgesia Task Force, 1999 (Box 25)
        - Toys "R" Us Check Presentation, 1994 (Box 25)
        - Vascular Access Patient Educational Services, 1999 (Box 25)
      - Soviet Patient prints, 1989; negatives (Box 25)
      - Superstars, 1997 (Box 25)
      - West Ann Arbor Clinic Opening, 1996 (Box 25)
    - Plastic Surgery
      - Sample, undated (Box 25)
    - Primary Care
      - Beyer Hospital Site, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Dr. Mitrovich at East Ann Arbor, 1996 (Box 25)
      - East Ann Arbor Clinic Grand Opening, 1996 (Box 25)
      - New Site Invitation [includes Drs. Zosnick, Denno, Meridian, and Reichert), 1997 (Box 25)
      - Saline Health Center Tour, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Saline Open House, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Stockbridge Clinic, Drs. Stevens and Smith, 1998 (Box 25)
    - Programs and Operations, 1996 (Box 25)
    - Psychiatry
      - 10th Annual Advances in Psychiatry, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Award Winners, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Barton Hills Graduate Dinner, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Behavioral Medical Program/Briarwood, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Behrent and Bieliauskas in Office, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Book Presentation, 1997 (Box 25)
      - Brochure
        - (Residency Training Program in Psychiatry), 1994 (Box 25)
        - 2000 (Box 25)
        - (Residents Brochure, Dr. Mellow and Trainees), 2000 (Box 25)
        - 2001 (Box 25)
      - Center for Forensic Psychiatry, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Chelsea Arbor Treatment Center, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Dr. Alessi Group, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Dr. Alessi plus 2 Group, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Dr. Jibson for Psychiatry Website, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Dr. Riba for Website, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Graduation
        - 1997 (Box 25)
        - 1999 (Box 25)
        - 2000 (Box 25)
        - 2001 (Box 25)
      - Group, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Jerry Lewis "Laughter and Healing,", 1997 (Box 25)
      - Lab Equipment, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Lunch and Learn, 2000 (Box 25)
      - "Never Too Old to Learn.", 1996 (Box 25)
      - Psychiatry Educators Conference, 1997 (Box 25)
      - Psychiatry Group and Individuals, 2001 (Box 25)
      - Psychiatry Group in Conference, 1999 (Box 25)
      - Riverview Adult Outpatient Clinic
        - 1999 (Box 25)
        - (Residents, etc.), 2000 (Box 25)
      - Situational Portraits, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Speaker/Award-Adolescent Sport Lecture, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Stress, Pain, and Depression Symposium, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Telemedicine Conference, 1997 (Box 25)
      - Traverwood Buildings, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Waggoner Lecture, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Web Page, 1999 (Box 25)
    - Psychology, 1998 (Box 25)
    - Public Relations
      - Andrew Radtke Day, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Forum on Health Care, 1994 (Box 25)
      - Medical School Website Redesign, 2001 (Box 25)
      - Picnic Orientation for New Medical School Class, 2001 (Box 25)
      - Sickle Cell, 1994 (Box 25)
    - Pulmonary
      - American Lung Association (ALA)
        - 1991 (Box 25)
        - (Drs. Green, Simon, Scott), 1991 (Box 25)
        - (Location Portraits for Brochure), 1991 (Box 25)
        - 1994 (Box 25)
        - Toews/Meyer, 1989 (Box 25)
      - MPV, 1994 (Box 25)
      - Pediatrics Pulmonary News Letter, 1995 (Box 25)
      - Specimen, 1996 (Box 25)
    - Radiation Oncology
      - Brochure, 2001 (Box 25)
      - Faculty and Residents, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Front Entrance, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Lichter Unveiling, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Residency Booklet, 1995 (Box 25)
    - Radiology
      - Dow Auditorium 2 Groups, 2000 (Box 25)
      - Operating Room Aortic Bypass, 1999 (Box 25)
    - Reproductive Sciences, 1994 (Box 25)
    - Respiratory Therapy
      - Dr. Wege and C. Haas, 1997 (Box 25)
      - Equipment, 1992 (Box 25)
      - Products, 1998 (Box 25)
      - Respiratory Therapy Week, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Rheumatology
      - Arthroscopic Surgery, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Ervin Fox and Group Location Portrait, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Stock Slides, 1995 (Box 25)
      (includes one representative binder with index of slides depicting University of Michigan and BMC logos, Ann Arbor and the University of Michigan campus, the University of Michigan Hospitals to be used in BMC publications)
    - Student and Faculty candid shots, unidentified, undated (Box 26)
    - Surgery
      - 4th Annual Conrad Jobs Lecture, 1993 (Box 26)
      - 150th anniversary publication materials, various dates, negatives, prints, slides (Box 26)
      - 150th Dow Speakers, 1999 (Box 26)
      - 150th Surgery Operating Room [Drs. Sweeney and Gratziano], 2000 (Box 26)
      - Advances in Surgery, 1990; negatives (Box 26)
      - Alexander Society, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 26)
      - Association for Academic Surgery (AAS) Conference, 1995 (Box 26)
      - Biomechanics Open House, 1989; negatives (Box 26)
      - Blood Clots, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Book Model and Authors, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Brochure, 1989; negatives (Box 26)
      - Bryant, Milton F. Lectureship
        - (Reception), 1994 (Box 26)
        - 1995 (Box 26)
        - (Award), 1998 (Box 26)
      - Cardiac Surgery Dr. Edward Bove (prints), 2000 (Box 26)
      - Catheters
        - 1991 (Box 26)
        - 1993 (Box 26)
      - Chief Residents
        - 1997 (Box 26)
        - Dinner
          - 1995 (Box 26)
          - 1996 (Box 26)
          - 1997 (Box 26)
          - 1998 (Box 26)
          - 1999 (Box 26)
          - 2000 (Box 26)
          - 2001 (Box 26)
        - Reception, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Chrysler Center Lobby, 2001 (Box 26)
      - Cocktail party and dinner, Michigan Union, 1991; contact sheet only (Box 26)
      - Coller Society
        - 1994 (Box 26)
        - Meeting and Tailgate, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Conn Meeting, 1994 (Box 26)
      - Crisler 150th Dinner, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Cymes and Jones, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Dinner Party Candids, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Dr. Bove 150th Surgery Publication, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Dr. Coran and Patient, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Dr. Mul Endowment Professorship, 1996 (Box 26)
      - Dr. Mulholland on Rounds, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Drs. Bartlett, Awad, Rich, General Surgery, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Drs. Thompson and Burney for Annual Report, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Endowment Wall Dedication, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Equipment, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Filter Retriever Series, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Filters in Specimens, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Gardner Child Award
        - 1994 (Box 26)
        - 1995 (Box 26)
        - 1997 (Box 26)
      - General Surgery Dr. John Sweeney (prints), 2000 (Box 26)
      - Grand Rounds: Crowne Plaza, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Greenfield Filters, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Greenfield Presenting Award, 1998 (Box 26)
      - Groups in Conference Room, 1997 (Box 26)
      - Gunn, Moses Conference
        - 1991 (Box 26)
        - 1992 (Box 26)
        - 1993 (Box 26)
        - 1994 (Box 26)
        - 1995 (Box 26)
        - 1998 (Box 26)
        - 1999 (Box 26)
      - Poster Session, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Hall of Fame, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Halsted Meeting, 1994 (Box 26)
      - Hands on Museum, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Harry Belfonte Dinner at Inglis House, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Heart Filter Equipment, 1991; negatives (Box 26)
      - Heart Filters in Specimens, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Jobst dinner with Dr. DeBakey, 1990; negatives (Box 26)
      - Jobst lecture and dinner, 1991; negatives (Box 26)
      - Kidney Transplant
        - 150th Surgery Celebration, 2000; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - 2000 (Box 26)
      - Lab Shots, 1995 (Box 26)
      - Latex clots, 1991; negatives (Box 26)
      - Mayo Lecture
        - Lecture and Dinner, 1991 (Box 26)
        - 1992 (Box 26)
        - 1994, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - (Speaker Dr. Debos), 1999 (Box 26)
      - Orringer with Patient, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Ortho[Orthopaedic] Research Lab, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Party
        - (Winter), 1991 (Box 26)
        - (Winter), 1992 (Box 26)
        - 1993 (Box 26)
        - 1994 (Box 26)
        - (Winter), 1994 (Box 26)
        - 1995(?) (Winter) (Box 26)
      - Plaque presentations, 1990; negatives (Box 26)
      - Presidential Address, 2000 (Box 26)
      - Reception at Michigan League, undated; negatives (Box 26)
      - Research Conference (speaker Casey), 1990; negatives (Box 26)
      - Slides, 1988 (Box 26)
      - Surgery, (includes black and white prints of operating room procedures), undated (Box 26)
      - Surgery Residents Dinner, 1999 (Box 26)
      - [Surgical apparatus], undated; prints and negatives (Box 26)
      - T.O.S. Stretch, 1999 (Box 26)
      - VA Hospital Surgery Group, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Worn Surgical Joint, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Young Investigator Award, 2000 (Box 26)
    - Surgery Graphics, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Survival Flight, 1985; 1993; undated
      - John Toomosions, photographer, 1984; prints, slides, negatives (Box 27)
      - 10th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 27)
      - Slides, 1991 (Box 27)
    - Thoracic Surgery
      - Dr. Mark Orringer (prints), 2000 (Box 27)
      - John Alexander Society Reunion, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Towsley Center [?], 1974
      - Negatives
        - Dean Gronvall and Staff (Box 27)
        - Dr. Bruce Work OB GYN (Box 27)
        - Dr. Baublis, Dr. Olsen, Dr. Wilson (Faculty) (Box 27)
        - Dr. Judge (Box 27)
        - Dr. Gosling (Box 27)
        - Dr. Towsley (Box 27)
        - Dr. Vanslow's Secretaries (Box 27)
        - Ed Sherman (Box 27)
        - Extramural (Box 27)
        - Faculty (Box 27)
        - Furstenberg Study Center (Box 27)
        - Independent Study Unit (Box 27)
        - Intramural Continuing Education (Box 27)
        - Med T.V. (Box 27)
        - Medical Illustration (Box 27)
        - O.E.R. 2 (Box 27)
        - O.E.R. 2 Asst. Director (Box 27)
        - O.E.R. Staff Meeting (Box 27)
        - Support and Business Office (Box 27)
      - Prints (Box 27)
        (Identified Subjects include: Baublis, Dekornfield, Gosling, Gronvall, Hiss, Johnson, Robert D., Johnson, Tom, Judge, Olson, William, Towsley, Wilson, Robert, Work)
      - Prints and Negatives
        - Chairman's Office/Office of Extramural Education, undated
          - Biomedical Communications, undated (Box 27)
          - Office of Continuing Medical Education, undated (Box 27)
            (Identified Subjects include: Elyse Buchanen, Jan Doten)
          - Office of Educational Resources and Research, undated (Box 27)
            (Identified Subjects include: Amy Butchart, Deb Kloska, Lorraine Maxfield, Mary Pappas, Judith Voelk, Nancy Weber)
    - Transfer Facility, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Transplant Administration, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Transplant Brochure
      - 1989 (Box 27)
      - 1989, undated (Box 27)
      - 1990 (Box 27)
    - Transplant House, 1990 (Box 27)
    - Turner Geriatric Center, 1992 (Box 27)
    - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine (ULAM)
      - Dr. Crisp Action Shot, 1990 (Box 27)
      - Weg CCMU (Critical Care Medical Unit), 1990 (Box 27)
    - University Hospital School-Children (Box 27)
    - University of Michigan-Flint Health Sciences, 2001; negatives (Box 27)
    - Urology
      - Dr. Donahue -- visiting professor, 1996 (Box 27)
      - Dr. John (Jack) Cichon (prints), 1998 (Box 27)
      - Dr. Smith Plaque and Group, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Dr. Walsh, John Hopkins Medical Center Lecturer at University of Michigan, 1995 (Box 27)
      - Equipment, 1993 (Box 27)
      - Groups Ford Amphitheater, 1998 (Box 27)
      - Lab Equipment, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Penile Prosthesis, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Pienta, Dr. Kenneth J., 1998; 1999; 3 folders (Box 27)
      - Procedure Materials, 1997 (Box 27)
      - Radiation Monitor, 1993 (Box 27)
      - Residents Dinner
        - 1991 (Box 27)
        - 1992 (Box 27)
      - Surgery 150th Anniversary, 1998 (Box 27)
      - Vasectomy Procedure, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Vascular Surgery
      - Bryant Lecture
        - 2000 (Box 27)
        - 2001 (Box 27)
      - Bryant Lectureship, 1997 (Box 27)
      - Burguer, Greenfield, and Stanley, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Jobst Lectureship, 1999 (Box 27)
      - Lindenaur Award, 1997 (Box 27)
      - Vascular Surgery Reception, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Ward and Hospital Photographs, undated; 2 folders prints, slides and negatives (Box 27)
    - X-rays, undated; prints and negatives (Box 27)
  - Non-Medical Related Topical Files
    - Architecture
      - Architecture and Urban Planning '99 Graduation, 1999 (Box 27)
      - Architecture Models (Box 27)
      - John Dinkeloo Memorial Lecture, 1996 (Box 27)
      - Rene Davids Lecture, 1997 (Box 27)
      - Reviewing Modernism. Allies + Morrison, 1997 (Box 27)
      - Sun. Arch. Models, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Susan Bryan: Models of Architecture, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Art School
      - Art and Design, 2000 (Box 27)
      - Yaffee Project, 1996 (Box 27)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Association of Multicultural Sciences, 9 items (Box 27)
      - 1999
        (headshots, listed individually)
    - Benefits
      - Staff Benefits Group, 1996 (Box 27)
    - Botany Department, 1929; undated (Box 27)
    - Building Services, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Business School
      - Murder Mystery Dinner, 1996 (Box 27)
      - Picnic, 1999 (Box 27)
      - The Rock, undated (Box 27)
    - Center for International Business Education (CIBE)
      - Brochure, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Business Professors/Students, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Executive Education Seminar, undated (Box 27)
      - Faculty Visitors, 1996 (Box 27)
      - Heinrich, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Seminar with Gunter Dufey, 1992 (Box 27)
    - Center for Japanese Studies
      - Open House, 1998 (Box 27)
      - Reception, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Center for Parallel Computing, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Center for Research on Ethnic Culture, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT), 1999 (Box 27)
    - Detroit Observatory, 1999 (Box 28)
    - Development Office
      - Affirmative Action, 2001 (Box 28)
      - Bentley Luncheon, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Board Group, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Community Health Promotion, 1999 (Box 28)
      - Crew Lab, 1999 (Box 28)
      - Faculty Awards
        - 1999 (Box 28)
        - 2001 (Box 28)
      - Ford Cheque, 1999 (Box 28)
      - Fundraisers' Party, 2001 (Box 28)
      - Gunner Berkheits, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Hass Scholar, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Honorary Degree Dinner
        - 1999 (Box 28)
        - 2001 (Box 28)
      - Michigan Daily and Student Publications, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Nobel Laureate, 1999 (Box 28)
      - President's Club Tailgate, 2001 (Box 28)
      - President's Group, 1999 (Box 28)
      - President's House, 1999 (Box 28)
      - President's Tailgate, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Roy Muir Retirement Party, 1998 (Box 28)
      - School of Social Work Endowed Chair, 1999 (Box 28)
      - Staff Meeting, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Walgreen Scholars, 20001 (Box 28)
    - Electrical Engineering (EECS)
      - Equipment, 1993 (Box 28)
      - Eugen Ghisson in Classroom, 1991 (Box 28)
      - Lab Dedication, 1996 (Box 28)
      - Nguyen with chip, 1997 (Box 28)
      - Software Lab, 1999 (Box 28)
    - Engineering Communications
      - Amy Chen and Dr. Cohen with America's Cup Hull, 1994 (Box 28)
      - Brochure, Walking Tour, 1993 (Box 28)
      - College of Engineering Employee Appreciation
        - Award Winners, 1995 (Box 28)
        - Reception, 1995 (Box 28)
      - Computer Lab with Ken Powell/Scholarship Recruits and Alumni, 1994 (Box 28)
      - Franois-Xavier Bagnoud (FXB) Building
        - Atrium Interior, 1993 (Box 28)
        - Construction, 1993 (Box 28)
      - W.M. Keck Plaque, 1995 (Box 28)
    - Executive Education
      - Award Recipient, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Geiger Group, 1998 (Box 28)
      - Group
        - 1998 (Box 28)
        - 1999 (Box 28)
        - (Group of Staff), Undated (Box 28)
      - Individual Portraits, 1999 (Box 28)
      - Joe Leotta Graduation, 2000 (Box 28)
      - MII Shrp. Classes, 1997 (Box 28)
      - Oxford Housing Kitchen, 1999 (Box 28)
      - Staff Portraits, 1997 (Box 28)